# Kavita Shivaji Kotekar

Email: <u>kavita.kotekar43@gmail.com</u> (Mobile) 9664820614

# **SUMMARY**

Catalog Executive with 4 year 10 months of comprehensive exposure to Ecommerce. Wide experience of handling all the stages of Catalog Executive Escalations.

My strength lies in delivering organizational expectations while working along with the employees as a team and work for their growth and knowledge enhancement.

## **Professional Experience**

Organization Name: Lumina Datamatics 22<sup>nd</sup> May 2017 To Till date.

**Designation: Senior Ecommerce Executive** 

Role and responsibilities: Worked For International Marketplace (WALMART).

Catalog Management.

Product categorization, attributes and attribute values

Creating category structure and defining its attributes.

Ensuring products placed on the e-retail sites are relevant to category and content

guidelines and SOP's are met.

Market research.

Upload the correct categorization bulk data on the Tool name of Editorial.

Tag the product in correct categorization.

Give the right product type.

Shelf Audit. (Category Analysis).

Reattribution: product main features updating in bulk source like product

Color, size, brand, subcategory and many more.

Daily Work Report generation.

Organization Name: MES India Sourcing Pvt. Ltd.(Wonderkids).1stAugust 2014 To 20th May 017.

**Designation: Catalog Executive** 

Role and responsibilities: Create Catalog New Products.

Renaming

Create Product Tittle, Description Short Descrption, Price updation Iamge

Order management & acceptance from multiple marketplaces + in house.)

Billing and inventory import /export Process Tools which was used UNICOMMERCE

as well as **BROWNTAPE**.

Create a contents or copy, edit and proof-read all web contents. (PRODUCT

**CATALOG CREATION**)

Will handle panels on Amazon, Flipkart, Shopclues Paytm, Snapdeal, Naaptol etc.

Liaising with internal departments, internal teams & warehouse

Liaising with vendors, for delivery & dispatches, logistics partner, printers and any other associated parties that need assistance with.

Reports preparation, monthly sales report, weekly stock update, sample tracking, payment tracking etc.

Oraganization Name: eSoft Technologies Pvt. Ltd. 31st July 2012 to 15th May 2014.

**Designation: Catalog Executive** 

**Role and responsibilities:** Worked on live website for US Client.(LifeandHome.Com)

Product Information Upload through the tool (MAGENTO)

Data Entry/ Manipulation.

Content & Image Updation.

Brand & Manufacture Research.

Also Involved in website analysis to ensure data is correctly represented and interpreted

online.

Daily Report.

# Oraganization Name: Etisalat DB Telecom Pvt. Ltd. 8th June 2010 To 31st March 2012.

**Designation: Back Office (Data Entry) Executive** 

Role and responsibilities: Image Audit & Data Entry Of Customer Application From InEdoc's System.

To Check the Quality of data entry (QC.)

Customer Details Check InOmnidocs& CRM (Customer Relationship Management).

Verification Of Sim Swap Documents.

# **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION**

Qualification	University	Class	Year
T.Y.B.A	Mumbai University	Second Class	2013
H.S.C	Mumbai University	Second Class	2008
S.S.C	Mumbai University	Second Class	2006

### ADDITIONAL TECHNICAL KNOWLEDGE

MS Office

DTP

Trained In Documentation Policy As Per TRAI (Telecom Regulatory Authority of India).

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Date of Birth : 8/8/1991.

Languages known : Marathi, Hindi, English.

Marital Status : Single.

Current Address : 7<sup>th</sup> Floor, Flat No.705, Om VajareshwariGajananCo.Op.Soc,

Gorai Road Near Fire Brigade, Borivali (West), Mumbai – 400092

Hobbies : Watching CN & Making Handcraft

Date : / /

Palace: Mumbai